Guide to the Tiger's Eye Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Tiger's Eye records
1939-1955
YCAL MSS 362
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
26
(57 boxes)
The records document all aspects of the production and distribution of the little magazine The Tiger's Eye, from its inception in 1947 through the decision to cease publication in 1951. Correspondence, manuscripts, and business records document the creative and editorial process, the enthusiasm of its readership, its subscription base, and the work involved in producing and distributing the issues.
Tiger's Eye
Stephan, John Walter, 1906-1995
Stephan, Ruth, 1910-1974
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Ruth and John Stephan, 1958; Gift of Ruth W. Franklin, 1971.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
The Tiger's Eye (1947-1949)
The little magazine The Tiger's Eye was founded in New York in 1947 by the poet Ruth Walgreen Stephan (1910-1974) and her husband, the painter John Stephan (1906-1995), and in its short existence earned acclaim for its discerning exposure of contemporary art and literature. Taking its title from William Blake, the magazine published the work of artists and writers both established and unknown, and documented the New York art world as well as international art movements, with particular emphasis on abstract expressionism. Its editorial selection process was based on the questions, "Is it alive? Is it valid as art? How brave is its originality? How does it enter the imagination?" (Issue 1, October 1947). The magazine did not publish reviews, and content was presented without immediate attribution so that readers could experience the works without preconception, although a list of contributors was included. Each issue was organized around a theme, such as modern sculpture, Peruvian art, or "the sublime."
The Tiger's Eye was published in nine quarterly issues between October 1947 and October 1949, when publication was suspended because the work became too much for the Stephans to manage. They initially intended to bring out further issues, but by 1951 realized that it would not be possible.
Scope and Contents
The records document all aspects of the production and distribution of the little magazine The Tiger's Eye, from its inception in 1947 through the decision to cease publication in 1951. Correspondence, manuscripts, and business records document the creative and editorial process, the enthusiasm of its readership, its subscription base, and the work involved in producing and distributing the issues.
Arrangement
Organized into five series: I. Correspondence, 1939-1955. II. Index Cards, 1947-1951. III. Manuscripts, 1947-1949. IV. Business Records, 1947-1951. V. 1971 Addition, 1946-1951.
Tiger's eye; Art -- Periodicals; Authors and publishers -- United States; Editors -- United States; Literature -- Periodicals; Little magazines -- Archives; Periodicals -- Publishing -- United States; Editors; Albers, Josef, 1888-1976; Abel, Lionel; Aiken, Conrad, 1889-1973; Arp, Jean, 1887-1966; Barnard, Mary; Barrault, Jean-Louis, 1910-1994; Bataille, Georges, 1897-1962; Borges, Jorge Luis, 1899-1986; Brooks, Van Wyck, 1886-1963; Char, René, 1907-1988; Crews, Judson, 1917-2010; Cummings, E. E. (Edward Estlin), 1894-1962; Dodson, Owen, 1914-1983; Eberhart, Richard, 1904-2005; Eliot, T. S. (Thomas Stearns), 1888-1965; Ernst, Max, 1891-1976; Fitts, Dudley, 1903-1968; Ford, Charles Henri, 1908-2002; Garrigue, Jean, 1912-1972; Genet, Jean, 1910-1986; Gregory, Horace, 1898-1982; Hays, H. R. (Hoffman Reynolds), 1904-1980; Laughlin, James, 1914-1997; MacIver, Loren, 1909-1998; Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972; Moss, Stanley; Neruda, Pablo, 1904-1973; Nin, Anaïs, 1903-1977; Pasternak, Boris Leonidovich, 1890-1960; Prévert, Jacques, 1900-1977; Queneau, Raymond, 1903-1976; Rexroth, Kenneth, 1905-1982; Roethke, Theodore, 1908-1963; Roskolenko, Harry, 1907-1980; Seligmann, Kurt, 1900-1962; Stamos, Theodoros, 1922-1997; Tyler, Parker, 1904-1974; Stephan, John Walter, 1906-1995; Stephan, Ruth, 1910-1974; Vazakas, Byron; Weber, Brom, 1917-1998; Wilbur, Richard, 1921-2017; Williams, William Carlos, 1883-1963; Wright, Richard, 1908-1960; Young, Marguerite, 1908-1995
- Series I: Correspondence, [1939]-1955; 12; (29 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Correspondence is organized into six subseries: Correspondence with Authors, General Correspondence, Correspondence regarding Distribution, Correspondence regarding Subscriptions, Correspondence with Subscription Agents, and Correspondence with Booksellers.
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence documents the editorial work of the magazine, including solicitation of content, and the business of distribution to individual subscribers, agents, booksellers. Outgoing carbon copies of letters from the Stephans, their associate editors, and their staff are frequently present in the files. Correspondence from contributors occasionally includes manuscripts. The General Correspondence subseries includes a mix of inquries about contributions, rejections, and exchanges with potential subscribers, as well as blank stationery, ephemera concerning art exhibitions, and other miscellaneous material. Correspondence regarding Distribution includes orders for single issues and distribution of complimentary copies, and documents the suspension of publication and refunds given in 1949 through 1951. Correspondence regarding subcriptions, with agents, and with booksellers documents individual subcribers to the magazine as well as the venues in which it was available for sale.
  Additional correspondence can be found in Series IV. Business Records.
  - Correspondence with Authors
    - Abel, Lionel, 1947 May, undated (Box 1)
    - Ackerman, Gerald, 1948 May 3 (Box 1)
    - Adan, Martin, undated (Box 1)
    - Aiken, Conrad, 1948-1949 (Box 1)
    - Albers, Josef and Anni, 1949-1951 (Box 1)
    - Albright, Ivan, 1949 September 4 (Box 1)
    - Apter, Howard, 1949, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Arguedas, José Mariá, 1947, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Arp, Hans, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Atkins, John, 1948-1951, undated (Box 1)
    - Attaway, William, undated (Box 1)
    - Barnard, Mary, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Baroff, Gene, 1947-1950, undated (Box 1)
    - Barrault, Jean-Louis, 1948 January (Box 1)
    - Barry, Francis, 1947-1948 (Box 1)
    - Bataille, Georges, 1947, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Bauman, Doris, 1947-1950, undated (Box 1)
    - Baziotes, William, 1948, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Bemberg, Georges, 1947-1948 (Box 1)
    - Berne, Stanley Lawrence, 1948-1950 (Box 1)
    - Bewly, Marius, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
    - Blair, Arthur, undated (Box 1)
    - Blake, Christopher, 1948-1951 (Box 1)
    - Block, Allan, 1947-1951, undated (Box 1)
    - Bondy, Sebastián Salazar, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
    - Borges, Jorge Luis, 1948-1950 (Box 1)
    - Borisoff, Paul, 1948-1949 (Box 1)
    - Boulton, Inez, 1949-1951 (Box 1)
    - Boyars, Arthur, 1949, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Bourgeois, Louise, 1949 May 2 (Box 1)
    - Brinnen, John Malcolm, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
    - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1942-1950, undated (Box 1)
    - Brower, C. V., 1949-1951 (Box 1)
    - Burford, William, 1949, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Burke, Marie Louise, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
    - Burrow, Trigant (The Lifwynn Foundation), 1947-1951 (Box 1)
    - Byrd, Richard E., 1949-1950 (Box 1)
    - Cage, John, 1948-1949 (Box 1)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1943 May 8 (Box 1)
    - Calas, Nicolas, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
    - Cahoon, Herbert, 1947-1951, undated; 2 (Box 1)
    - Campbell, Joseph, 1949 May 25 (Box 2)
    - Carreño, Mario, 1947-1949, undated (Box 2)
    - Carrier, William, 1948-1950, undated (Box 2)
    - Char, René, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Chew, Richard H., 1947-1950 (Box 2)
    - Cirlot, Juan Eduardo, 1948-1950 (Box 2)
    - Clements, Albert, 1947-1949 (Box 2)
    - Cloud, Jess, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
    - Coates, Carrol, 1947-1951 (Box 2)
    - Cole, Thomas, 1947-1950 (Box 2)
    - Coleman, Lucille, 1948-1950 (Box 2)
    - Cook, Albert, 1947-1949 (Box 2)
    - Crews, Judson, 1947-1951 (Box 2)
    - Cummings, E. E. (Edward Estlin), 1951 March 16 (Box 2)
    - Dawkins, Mary Lucile, 1949-1951 (Box 2)
    - De Brun, Elsa, 1948, 1950 (Box 2)
    - DeJong, David Cornel, 1947-1951 (Box 2)
    - Deren, Maya, 1947-1956, undated (Box 2)
    - Deutsch, Babette, 1947-1950 (Box 2)
    - Dodson, Owen, 1947-1950 (Box 2)
    - Duncan, Harry, 1949, 1951 (Box 2)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1947, 1949, undated (Box 2)
    - Dunsmuir, Nessie, 1948-1949, undated (Box 2)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1947-1951 (Box 2)
    - Eielson, Jorge Eduardo, 1948-1950 (Box 2)
    - Eisler, Kenneth, 1948-1951 (Box 2)
    - Eliot, T. S. (Thomas Stearns), 1947-1954 (Box 2)
    - Elliott, George P., 1949 (Box 2)
    - Emerson, Richard Wirtz, 1948-1951 (Box 2)
    - Enright, D. J. (Dennis Joseph), 1947-1949 (Box 2)
    - Ernst, Max, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Everson, Landis, 1949, 1951 (Box 2)
    - Everson, William, 1948 (Box 2)
    - Fearing, Kenneth, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Ferber, Herbert, 1948 April 20 (Box 2)
    - Fitts, Dudley, 1947 (Box 2)
    - Flynn, Patrick, 1947 (Box 2)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
    - Frankenberg, Lloyd, 1947-1950 (Box 2)
    - Frechtman, Bernard, 1948-1951, undated (Box 2)
    - Frederick, Phyllis, 1948-1951, undated (Box 2)
    - Friedman, Howard R., 1950 October 26 (Box 2)
    - Friend, Robert, 1949-1950 (Box 2)
    - Frimet, Hillel, 1949-1950 (Box 2)
    - Garai, Pierre, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Garrigue, Jean, 1949-1950 (Box 2)
    - Genet, Jean, undated (Box 2)
    - Ghiselin, Brewster, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
    - Giacometti, Alberto, 1948 (Box 2)
    - Gianakoulis, Theodore, 1947-1951 (Box 2)
    - Girona, Inés, 1948 November (Box 2)
    - Godden, William, 1948-1951 (Box 3)
    - Golfing, Francis C., 1946-1949 (Box 3)
    - Goll, Yvon, 1949 March 29 (Box 3)
    - Goodman, Paul, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
    - Gorky, Arshile, undated (Box 3)
    - Graham, W. S. (William Sydney), 1947-1950 (Box 3)
    - Green, Ellen K., 1949 November 9 (Box 3)
    - Greer, Scott, 1947-1950 (Box 3)
    - Gregor, Arthur, 1947-1950 (Box 3)
    - Gregory, Horace, 1947-1948, undated (Box 3)
    - Griffin, Howard, 1949 September 30 (Box 3)
    - Grippe, Peter, 1948 April 12 (Box 3)
    - Gross, Ben, 1948 May 10 (Box 3)
    - Gross, John, 1949, 1951, undated (Box 3)
    - Hammid, Alexander, 1947-1951, undated (Box 3)
    - Hanson, K. O., 1947-1950 (Box 3)
    - Hare, David, 1950-1951 (Box 3)
    - Hauser, Marianne, 1947-1948 (Box 3)
    - Hayakawa, S. I. (Samuel Ichiyé), 1949-1950 (Box 3)
    - Hayden, Robert, 1948 (Box 3)
    - Hays, H. R. (Hoffman Reynolds), 1949, 1951 (Box 3)
    - Hayter, Stanley William, 1950 September (Box 3)
    - Higdon, Grace, 1947-1948 (Box 3)
    - Hokusai, Katsushika, undated (Box 3)
    - Holden, Harold, 1948-1949 (Box 3)
    - Holzhauer, Jean, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
    - Honig, Edwin, 1948-1950 (Box 3)
    - Huskins, Katherine, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
    - Hovhaness, Alan, 1950-1951 (Box 3)
    - Hugo, Ian, 1947, 1949 (Box 3)
    - Hull, William, 1948-1951 (Box 3)
    - John, George, 1951 March (Box 3)
    - Johnson, Una, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
    - Josephs, Laurence, 1949, 1951 (Box 3)
    - Kees, Weldon, 1947-1949, undated (Box 3)
    - Kelly, Leon, 1947 December 5 (Box 3)
    - Kent, Louis, 1949-1951 (Box 3)
    - Kiesler, Steffi, 1949 (Box 3)
    - Kochnitzky, Léon A., 1947-1950 (Box 3)
    - Koizumi, Kazuo, 1950 (Box 3)
    - Krim, Seymour, 1948-1949 (Box 3)
    - Lamantia, Philip, 1947-1951 (Box 3)
    - Lang, V. R., 1948-1951 (Box 3)
    - Laughlin, Clarence John, 1948-1951 (Box 3)
    - Laughlin, James, 1948-1951 (Box 3)
    - Lawson, John S., 1947-1948 (Box 3)
    - Libert, Jack, 1947-1950 (Box 3)
    - Lerman, Leo, 1947-1951 (Box 3)
    - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1948 April 8 (Box 3)
    - Lippold, Richard, 1948 (Box 3)
    - Lipton, Seymour, [1939] (Box 3)
    - Locker, Arthur P., 1949, 1951 (Box 3)
    - Loeb, Harold, 1949, 1951 (Box 3)
    - Lortz, Richard, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
    - Lye, Len, 1948-1951, undated (Box 3)
    - Maas, Willard, 1948-1951, undated (Box 3)
    - MacIver, Loren, 1949 (Box 3)
    - Maclaine, Christopher, 1948-1951, undated (Box 3)
    - McAfee, Tom, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
    - McElroy, Walter, 1949-1951 (Box 3)
    - McLaughlin, Richard, 1947, undated (Box 3)
    - Magner, Gene, 1948-1951, undated (Box 4)
    - Manheim, Ralph, 1947-1951 (Box 4)
    - Margo, Boris, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - Mason, August H., 1948-1951 (Box 4)
    - Mason, Mason Jason, 1951 March 15 (Box 4)
    - Masson, André, 1949 (Box 4)
    - Mathieu, George, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
    - Matthews, Robert, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
    - Mayhall, Jane, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - Mayo, E. L. (Edward L.), 1948-1950 (Box 4)
    - Merton, Thomas, 1947-1948 (Box 4)
    - Metcalf, Eleanor Melville, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
    - Michaux, Henri, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Miller, Warren, 1951 March 20 (Box 4)
    - Mitcham, Howard, 1949 (Box 4)
    - Mohn, Earl, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
    - Moir, Robert, 1948 July 7 (Box 4)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1947-1953 (Box 4)
    - Moore, Susan, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
    - Morgan, Maud, 1947-1948 (Box 4)
    - Morton, Bert, 1948-1951 (Box 4)
    - Moss, Stanley, 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - Motherwell, Robert, undated (Box 4)
    - Murch, Walter T., 1950 (Box 4)
    - Murray, Philip, 1947-1949 (Box 4)
    - Neider, Charles, 1947-1951 (Box 4)
    - Neiman, Gilbert, 1947-1949 (Box 4)
    - Nerber, John, 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - Neruda, Pablo, 1949 October 25 (Box 4)
    - Newman, Barnett B., 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - Nims, John Frederick, 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - Nin, Anaïs, 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - Norse, Harold, 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - O'Connor, Mary, 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - O'Higgins, Myron, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - Olson, Elder, 1948 February 8 (Box 4)
    - Orgel, Irene, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - Orlando, Felipe, 1947-1948 (Box 4)
    - Oster, Edward, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
    - Parks, Lloyd, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
    - Parrish-Martin, W. J., 1948-1951 (Box 4)
    - Pasternak, Boris Leonidovich, undated (Box 4)
    - Patchen, Kenneth, 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - Pendergast, Constance, 1948-1951 (Box 4)
    - Picasso, Pablo, undated (Box 4)
    - Pillin, William, 1947-1951 (Box 4)
    - Pitcher, Oliver, 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - Pousette-Dart, Richard, 1950 (Box 4)
    - Prévert, Jacques, 1950-1951 (Box 4)
    - Price, Robert G., 1947-1950 (Box 4)
    - Queneau, Raymond, 1947-1950 (Box 5)
    - Raab, Robert, 1948-1951 (Box 5)
    - Racz, André, 1949-1951 (Box 5)
    - Rago, Henry, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
    - Raymund, Bernard, 1947-1950 (Box 5)
    - Read, Herbert Edward, Sir, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
    - Reavey, George, 1950 (Box 5)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth, 1947-1951 (Box 5)
    - Rodewald, Douglas P., 1948-1951 (Box 5)
    - Roethke, Theodore, 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - Roscher, Don, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
    - Rosenberg, Harold, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
    - Roskolenko, Harry, 1947-1951 (Box 5)
    - Rubenstein, Richard, 1948-1951 (Box 5)
    - Rothko, Mark, 1950 (Box 5)
    - Ryan, Anne, 1950 September 14 (Box 5)
    - Saul, Milton, 1948-1951 (Box 5)
    - Schade, Dixon, 1949-1951 (Box 5)
    - Schaumann, Herbert, 1947 September 17 (Box 5)
    - Schevill, James Erwin, 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - Schliefer, Ben, 1947, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Schnabel, Day N., 1948 May 14 (Box 5)
    - Schochen, Seyril, 1948, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Schrag, Karl, 1950 January 24 (Box 5)
    - Schwartz, Shloime, 1947-1949 (Box 5)
    - Schwerner, Armand, 1949 (Box 5)
    - Seldon, Edwin S., 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - Seligmann, Kurt, 1949-1951 (Box 5)
    - Shelley, Robert, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
    - Simon, John, 1947-1949 (Box 5)
    - Siskind, Aaron, 1948 May 16 (Box 5)
    - Sjögren, Erik, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Smith, David, [1948] (Box 5)
    - Smith, William Jay, 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - Solomon, Marvin, 1948-1950 (Box 5)
    - Spender, Stephen, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
    - Stafford, William, 1947-1949 (Box 5)
    - Stamos, Theodoros, 1948-1950 (Box 5)
    - Stark, Elva June, 1948, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Steinaker, John, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Sterne, Hedda, 1947, 1950 (Box 5)
    - Still, Clyfford, 1949 January 2 (Box 5)
    - Strongin, Josephine, 1948-1950 (Box 5)
    - Stussman, Mort, 1948, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Sutherland, Donald, 1950-1951 (Box 5)
    - Sweeney, John L., 1948-1950 (Box 5)
    - Swetzoff, Hyman, 1948-1950 (Box 5)
    - Sylvester, A. D. B., 1948-1949 (Box 5)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 1947-1949 (Box 5)
    - Tanning, Dorothea, 1949-1950 (Box 5)
    - Taylor, K. P. A., 1949, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Tobey, Mark, 1950 May 18 (Box 5)
    - Todd, Ruthven, 1947, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Tomlin, Bradley, undated (Box 5)
    - Toyen, undated (Box 5)
    - Treece, Henry, 1951 March 15 (Box 5)
    - Triem, Eve, 1947-1951 (Box 5)
    - Tyler, Parker, 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - Vazakas, Byron, 1947-1949 (Box 6)
    - Viereck, Peter, 1947-1951, undated (Box 6)
    - Villa, José García, 1949, 1951 (Box 6)
    - Virtue, Vivian, 1946-1950 (Box 6)
    - Von Hagen, Victor Wolfgang, 1947-1951 (Box 6)
    - Wagoner, David, 1948-1949 (Box 6)
    - Wainhouse, Austryn, 1947-1949 (Box 6)
    - Weathers, Winston, 1947-1950 (Box 6)
    - Webster, Harvey Curtis, 1947-1948 (Box 6)
    - Weber, Brom, 1948-1951 (Box 6)
    - Weisenthal, Morris, 1947-1951 (Box 6)
    - Wesenberg, Alice Bidwell, 1949, 1951 (Box 6)
    - Westphalen, Emilio Adolfo, 1947-1951 (Box 6)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 1949-1950 (Box 6)
    - Wilbur, Richard, 1948-1950 (Box 6)
    - Williams, Gwyn, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
    - Williams, John, 1948-1949 (Box 6)
    - Williams, William Carlos, 1948-1950 (Box 6)
    - Wilson, T. C., 1948-1949 (Box 6)
    - Woelffer, Emerson, 1948-1949 (Box 6)
    - Wright, David, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
    - Wright, Richard, 1947 (Box 6)
    - Yonge, Theo, no year September 15 (Box 6)
    - Yorck, Ruth, 1948-1950 (Box 6)
    - Young, Marguerite, 1947-1950 (Box 6)
    - Young, Vernon, 1949-1951 (Box 6)
    - Yunkers, Adja, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
    - Zabriskie, George, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Zadkine, Ossip, 1946-1950 (Box 6)
    - Zaturenska, Marya, 1949-1951 (Box 6)
    - Zorn, Ray H., 1947-1949 (Box 6)
    - List of authors in first nine issues of Tiger's Eye, undated (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1950, undated (Box 6)
  - General Correspondence
    - "A", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "B", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "C", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "D", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "E", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "F", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "G", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "H", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "J", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "K", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "L", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "M", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "N", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "O", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "P", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "Q", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "R", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "S", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "T", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "U", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "V", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "W", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "X-Z", 1947 (Box 7)
    - "A", 1948 (Box 7)
    - "B", 1948; 2 (Box 7)
    - "C", 1948 (Box 7)
    - "D", 1948 (Box 7)
    - "E", 1948 (Box 7)
    - "F", 1948 (Box 7)
    - "G", 1948 (Box 7)
    - "H", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "I", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "J", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "L", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "M", 1948; 2 (Box 8)
    - "N", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "O", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "P", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "Q", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "R", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "S", 1948; 2 (Box 8)
    - "T", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "U", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "V", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "W", 1948; 2 (Box 8)
    - "X-Z", 1948 (Box 8)
    - "A", 1949 (Box 9)
    - "B", 1949; 3 (Box 9)
    - "C", 1949; 2 (Box 9)
    - "D", 1949 (Box 9)
    - "E", 1949 (Box 9)
    - "F", 1949 (Box 9)
    - "G", 1949 (Box 9)
    - "H", 1949; 2 (Box 9)
    - "I", 1949 (Box 10)
    - "J", 1949 (Box 10)
    - "K", 1949 (Box 10)
    - "L", 1949; 2 (Box 10)
    - "M", 1949; 3 (Box 10)
    - "N", 1949 (Box 10)
    - "O", 1949 (Box 10)
    - "P", 1949 (Box 10)
    - "R", 1949; 2 (Box 10)
    - "S", 1949; 2 (Box 11)
    - "T", 1949 (Box 11)
    - "U", 1949 (Box 11)
    - "V", 1949 (Box 11)
    - "W", 1949; 2 (Box 11)
    - "X-Z", 1949 (Box 11)
    - "A", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "B", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "C", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "D", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "E", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "F", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "G", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "H", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "I", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "J", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "K", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "L", 1950 (Box 11)
    - "M", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "N", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "O", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "P", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "R", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "S", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "T", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "U-V", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "W", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "X-Z", 1950 (Box 12)
    - "A-B", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "C", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "D", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "E", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "F", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "G", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "H", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "I-J", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "K", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "L", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "M", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "N", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "O-P", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "R", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "S", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "T", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "U", 1951 (Box 13)
    - "V-Z", 1951 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 13)
    - Art announcements, 1947-1948 (Box 13)
    - Book stores list, undated (Box 13)
    - Editorial - miscellaneous, 1950 March 20 (Box 13)
    - Letters - books of poetry, 1947-1948, undated (Box 13)
    - Letters - Poetry Bulletin Review, 1950 (Box 13)
    - Poetry Bulletin copies, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
    - Stationery sampler for Ruth Stephan Films, undated (Box 13)
    - Suggestions, 1947 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Stephan material, [1947] (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Tiger's Eye printed forms, undated (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence regarding distribution
    - Single Issue #1 - Paid, 1947-1950; 3 (Box 14)
    - Single Issue #2 - Paid, 1947-1950 (Box 14)
    - Single Issue #3 - Paid, 1948-1950 (Box 14)
    - Single Issue #4 - Paid, 1948-1950 (Box 14)
    - Single Issue #5 - Paid, 1948-1951 (Box 14)
    - Single Issue #6 - Paid, 1948-1951; 2 (Box 14)
    - Single Issue #7 - Paid, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
    - Single Issue #8 - Paid, 1949-1951 (Box 14)
    - Single Issue #9 - Paid, 1949-1951; 2 (Box 14)
    - Single issues - unpaid bills, 1948-1950; 2 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #1; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, etc., 1947-1949 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #2; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, etc., 1947, 1949 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #3; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, 1948-1949 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issues #3; samples sent to bookstores, 1948; 2 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #4; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, etc., 1948 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #5; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, etc., 1948-1950 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #6; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, etc., 1948-1950 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #7; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, etc., 1949-1950 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #8; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, etc., 1949-1950 (Box 15)
    - Free copies - Issue #9; review, exchange, sample advance complimentary copies, etc., 1949-1951 (Box 15)
    - Correspondence concerning refunds, 1950-1951; 2 (Box 16)
    - Correspondence - suspension of magazine, 1950-1951 (Box 16)
    - Addressograph plates, 1949-1951 (Box 16)
    - Billing records to dealers, 1950 (Box 16)
    - College subscription fund, 1948-1950 (Box 16)
    - Complimentary sets of Tiger's Eye sent to universities and museums, 1951 (Box 16)
    - Future complimentary copies, 1950 (Box 16)
    - Future reference - single issue, 1950-1951 (Box 16)
    - Future reference - subscription file, 1950-1951; 2 (Box 16)
    - Requests for back issues instead of refunds, 1950-1951 (Box 16)
    - Subscription bills, 1948-1950; 3 (Box 16)
    - Subscription invoice - waiting for remittance, 1949-1951 (Box 16)
    - Subscription refund list, 1951 (Box 16)
  - Correspondence regarding subscriptions